It has begun. Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series.
We, Super Turn! Strong Energy! Positively Exciting! Soulful Rom! I'm Yuzuki Daikoku, a purple/purple-colored member of Nagoya Team Shaqi! I'm Yuzuki Daikoku, the purple/purple-colored Yuzuki of Nagoya Team Shaqi!
Please give me your best regards.
And,
Yes, I am Director Yoshinori Uka Nomura. I'm Yoshi Nomura, a member of the board of directors of Uka Nomura.
It's been a while.
It's been a long time.
I've met Director-chan and she has been to my weekly Winter Moon Room,
And you have also appeared twice at the Hair Fest, so thank you very much.
Some memorable event?
If you have performed in 21 years,
Yuzuki-chan and I sang and danced together at Monday Kuji no Yoru,
Yuzuki-chan's voice was really cool,
I'm so happy! Thank you!
You sang the first verse of the song with Yuzuki-chan, didn't you?
Yes, in the chorus.
I thought it was great, and it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun.
I was just distributing the video at the time,
And Yuzuki's Hair Festival itself,
I think it was the first time we held the festival.
It was one of the events where I felt that we were able to work together and get to know more people, even if just a little bit,
Yuzuki's Room as well.
That's right.
With Ayame.
That's right. I was able to perform with Ayame.
Do you see Ayame often?
Ayame is always having tea with me.
I think so.
Really, Riz, how was it? Yuzuki's room.
It was quite a while ago.
Yes, about two years ago,
We answered quizzes together,
I had a lot of fun talking with Setoguchi-san,
I would like to appear on the show again,
I want you to be on the show!
Last time, A-chan came to the show,
I have not been able to complete the list yet, so my manager and I were asked to do a Uka special,
We were even talking about having all of us perform together,
If you could please do it, I would really appreciate it.
Please do so.
So, I would like to have fun with Riz-chan.
We were told to prepare questions that we would like to ask each other,
I would like to answer the questions that we have prepared for each other.
First of all, I have a question for Riz-chan.
Please ask Riz-chan a question.
If you were to create a group with Rizu-chan as the leader, who would you include and what kind of concept would you like to create?
Let's say I am the leader of the group,
How many people in a group with Wakabayashi?
How many people in a group? Yes, we can be just the two of us, or we can be a group of two, or we can be a very large group.
Or we can have a very large group. How many people do you want?
We're at six right now, but let's think about a group of five. We can have a center.
I'd like to try a group of five.
Then, Rin Waka and, and I know it's presumptuous of me to call myself Rin, but Yuzuki and I... I want to go, so please go.
I want to go, so please go. I did it.
Yuzuki and I wonder who else.
I wonder who else would be good.
And Risyu, and two more.
The other two are Sakura Seta from the Battenshonjo-tai.
Oh! That's nice.OH!!! That's nice.
I'm a little curious about Sakura Seta, she likes anime and games.
I'm curious.
Wow, one! One! That's annoying! She is from quite a variety of groups.
A lot of local groups.
Then, Haruka Koizumi from Super Tokimeki Advertising.
What's that about?
Well, well, Waka Rin and Koharu are my personal friends.
They are the only two people in STAPLA that I get along with,
The other two are, um...
Do you get the impression that they're pretty calm?
Round.
Rounded.
That's the image I had in mind when I chose these five.
I hope it will come true again somewhere,
I would love to work with different groups like that, even if it's just for a day.
I was thinking that I would like to do something like that at a staple festival or something like that.
Like a shuffle unit.
I will do my best to make that happen.
Thank you.
Well, Rizu-chan.
I have a question for you,
What do you do before a live performance?
I was curious.
I really like idols before a live performance,
I like idols a lot, and I admire the way they look at me,
I often think that I want to be able to perform like them,
In order to improve my ability to express myself, I watch videos of my favorite idols,
I watch videos of idols I really like in order to improve my ability to express myself.
I watch videos of my favorite idols to improve my ability to express myself. Watch them,
I see this girl, for example, who can leave such a big mark in one second,
I want to be like her, so I raise my ambition and raise it,
I want to be like her, and I want to raise my aspirations to the max,
I feel like I can give a great live performance,
I do that too.
I do that a lot,
I do it on a daily basis.
That's right. I feel the same way,
I personally really like your performance,
I'm so happy!
First of all, your face is so cute, beautiful, and beautiful,
Your singing voice is also very cool, and I want to sing as cool as you do,
I've been listening to your songs,
You're good.
I'm not like that.
Why? Why?
It's not like that, but you're really good at faking it,
Embarrassing.
It's cool. I don't often do faking in my own group,
I admire it.
I admire Uka-chan's music,
I think of Uka's music as a genre,
It is easy to understand once you listen to it.
I wanted to try my hand at something like this.
That's right. Ucuka's music covers a wide range,
Even within a single song, the range from the lowest to the highest note is quite impressive,
It is sometimes difficult and I struggle with it every time,
I sometimes struggle with it, but next time I would like to try a cooler, more mature song,
I want to try to sing songs that have a mature sound, and since there are a lot of high notes in my songs, I want to try to sing low notes.
I want to sing with a low tone, and keep the tone low.
It's a bit darker than bright.It's a bit darker than bright.
I think the image of high notes is quite familiar,
But many of the members of Ukka are good at low tones,
I see.
Like Shin.
Many of the members have a voice like Shin,
I'd like to try something cool with that kind of low bass tone.
I want to see it so much!
And just one song would broaden the scope of your live performances,
Yes, that's true.
I'm already looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
One thing we have in common is that we both like Cinnamon. I also like Pom Pom Pudding.
She was the top two, right? How did you come to like Pom Pom Pudding?
When I realized that I liked Pom Pom Pudding when I was little.
The position of Pom Pom Pudding's eyes, nose, and mouth are very unique.
Unique! I used to like the character whose actual name is like a puppy dog.
Also, I used to eat a lot of pudding when I was little.
I see!
I felt that we had something in common, so I started liking Pom Pom Pudding... and I still do.
But why Cinnamon?
Cinnamon has always loved Sanrio.
I've always loved all kinds of characters.
But I guess it was inspiration.
I like the color light blue.
A lot of their goods are light blue, so I thought Cinnamon would be a good choice.
I was also attracted by the design.
And then I found myself watching Cinnamon cartoons and things like that.
And then...
I was quite taken by it. It's cute. It's really cute.
I'm interested in more and more characters.
I understand. Is there a character you're interested in?
I did a one-man show at Sanrio Puroland a while back.
We did it together with Kochakko and Kogimun.
Kogimun is kind of cute.
Kogimun is cute, but the shrimp on top of him is really cute.
I'm a little curious about the shrimp. Here? Not here?
Yes, I'm interested in this part. Some people seem to be drawn to the eyes.
The one with the eyes. The one with the fried prawn eyes and the black eyes.
He's cute.
I can see why you're attracted to the sub character. He's right next to Puddin'.
Isn't Muffin cute? He's cute. He's so cute.
Not so much. The main characters are usually the merchandise.
I like Cinnamon too, but you like Milk too.
I know, I know.
When I was a little girl, I liked Cinnamon.
I used to love the ones with Milk-kun on the side.
I understand.
Not just Pudding, but the whole set.
That's the way you see the world.
That's right.
It was a one-man show at Sanryo,
I saw the video of you and Chinabone meeting,
I saw her crying, and I could already understand how she felt.
Did you cry?
When I had my first solo live at Sanryo Kyuroland,
I took out a checkerboard over here,
That was the first time I met Puddin-chan,I met Puddin for the first time there,
I cried so hard,
It's the same thing.
I didn't think I would cry so much.
I wonder what it was like. I don't know.
I don't know.
They were so precious and cute,
That's right.
When we were posing, you know, when we were taking the heat shot together,
Chinabone was lifting one leg up on his heel.
I cried so hard because it was so cute,
I know.
I don't know. I wonder what his mentality was like at that moment.
I'd like to analyze it myself,
Puddin-chan was taking a picture with the members,
She was taking a picture with the members, and she put her hand down, but at the moment of taking the picture,
I was crying too,
That made me cry too.
I cried when she lifted her hand,
I was like, "Why are you crying? I was like, "Why are you crying?
But I guess it's the same for people who like Sanrio.
The point of crying is the same for Sanrio lovers.
That's right.
The second time, Rina Yuki, a member of the group, likes Tsutomu Koyoshi,
When she met Tsutomu Koyoshi, she cried,
I was thinking, "I know, I know, I know,
I thought to myself, "I see. I thought to myself, "I knew it.
So it's not that I'm crazy,
Everyone is.
I feel relieved.
I'm glad too.
I'm glad.
When I watch your videos, too,
I understand very much.
I was thinking that I was definitely like that too,
Let's go to Eiro land.
I want to go.
Many of the three Utsuka members like Sanrio.
There are many.
The two members don't go to the Sanrio store together this much,
Let's go.
I want to go.
Please do.
I'm looking forward to it.
So far, Rime-chan and I have talked about Sanrio and many other things,
I've been talking with Rime-chan about Sanrio talk and many other things, but I'm sure we'll have another video tomorrow,
I would like to talk more and more about fun things and get to know each other better.
Please look forward to tomorrow.
Bye bye!
This way.